<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Da Nang Treasure Hunt</string>

    <string name="madamLan_title">Madam Lan</string>
    <string name="madamLan_description">Madam Lan is a popular dining spot in Da Nang, offering a fusion of traditional Vietnamese and modern cuisine. The restaurant is known for its beautiful colonial-style architecture and a diverse menu featuring local specialties like "cao lau" and "banh xeo". It\'s perfect for those wanting to experience authentic Vietnamese flavors in an elegant setting.</string>
    <string name="madamLan_address">4 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="beMan_title">Be Man Seafood</string>
    <string name="beMan_description">Be Man Seafood Restaurant is one of Da Nang\'s most popular seafood spots, known for its extensive and fresh selection of seafood. The restaurant is large and bustling, ideal for groups and family gatherings. Guests can choose their seafood from tanks and have it prepared to their liking. The relaxed, open-air setting and friendly service add to the appeal.</string>
    <string name="beMan_address">Lot 11 Vo Nguyen Giap, Man Thai, Son Tra District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="bepTrang_title">Bep Trang</string>
    <string name="bepTrang_description">Bep Trang is famous for its unique and flavorful "My Quang" (a regional noodle dish) with frog meat. This dish is a must-try for visitors seeking authentic local cuisine. The restaurant prides itself on its handmade noodles and carefully crafted broth, which provide a rich and savory dining experience. The elegant yet cozy ambiance, along with attentive service, makes it a favorite among both locals and tourists.</string>
    <string name="bepTrang_address">K280/23 Hoang Dieu Street, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="namRanh_title">Hai San Nam Ranh</string>
    <string name="namRanh_description">Hai San Nam Ranh is renowned for its fresh and delicious seafood, making it a top choice for locals and visitors alike. The restaurant offers a wide variety of seafood dishes, all at reasonable prices. The vibrant atmosphere, friendly staff, and quick service enhance the dining experience, making it a must-visit for seafood lovers.</string>
    <string name="namRanh_address">401 Tran Hung Dao, Son Tra District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>

    <string name="sky36_title">Sky36 Bar</string>
    <string name="sky36_description">Sky36 Bar, located on the rooftop of the Novotel Danang Premier Han River, is the highest rooftop bar in Vietnam. It offers breathtaking panoramic views of Da Nang, making it a perfect spot to enjoy a cocktail while watching the sunset. The vibrant atmosphere, excellent music, and stylish decor attract both locals and tourists alike.</string>
    <string name="sky36_address">36 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="craftsman_title">The Craftsman Cocktail Bar</string>
    <string name="craftsman_description">The Craftsman Cocktail Bar is renowned for its expertly crafted cocktails and cozy ambiance. This hidden gem features a speakeasy vibe, making it a favorite among locals who appreciate a good drink in a relaxed and intimate setting. The bartenders are skilled mixologists, known for their creative and delicious concoctions.</string>
    <string name="craftsman_address">28 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="bamboo2_title">Bamboo 2 Bar</string>
    <string name="bamboo2_description">Bamboo 2 Bar is a beloved local hangout spot with a laid-back atmosphere and a great selection of beers and cocktails. Located near the Han River, it features live music, pool tables, and a welcoming vibe. It\'s a perfect place to unwind and socialize with both locals and expats.</string>
    <string name="bamboo2_address"> 216 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="topView_title">Top View Bar</string>
    <string name="topView_description">Top View Bar is a chic rooftop bar located at the Altara Suites Hotel. It offers stunning views of Da Nang city and the beach, providing a perfect backdrop for enjoying a cocktail. The bar is known for its elegant atmosphere, extensive drink menu, and excellent service, making it a favorite among locals looking for a sophisticated night out.</string>
    <string name="topView_address">120 Vo Nguyen Giap, Son Tra District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>

    <string name="factoryCoffee_title">43 Factory Coffee Roaster</string>
    <string name="factoryCoffee_description">43 Factory Coffee Roaster is a must-visit for coffee enthusiasts. Known for its specialty coffee and minimalist, industrial-style decor, it offers a unique coffee experience. The shop roasts its own beans, ensuring fresh and flavorful brews. It\'s a great spot for those looking to savor expertly crafted coffee in a trendy setting.</string>
    <string name="factoryCoffee_address">Lot 422, Ngo Thi Sy, My An, Ngu Hanh Son District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="utTich_title">Ca Phe Ut Tich</string>
    <string name="utTich_description">Ca Phe Ut Tich is known for its charming Hoi An-inspired decor, creating a nostalgic yet lively atmosphere. The coffee shop features a combination of traditional and modern elements, offering a peaceful retreat with gentle background music. It is an ideal spot for relaxing, studying, or catching up with friends. The menu includes a variety of delicious beverages, and the cafe is praised for its friendly and professional service.</string>
    <string name="utTich_address">100–102 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="congCoffee_title">Cafe Cong</string>
    <string name="congCoffee_description">Cafe Cong is part of a popular Vietnamese coffee chain known for its unique retro decor and cozy ambiance. The cafe offers a variety of drinks, but its signature "coconut coffee" is a standout. It\'s a great place to experience a nostalgic vibe while enjoying a delicious beverage.</string>
    <string name="congCoffee_address">96–98 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="aroiDessert_title">Aroi Dessert Cafe</string>
    <string name="aroiDessert_description">Aroi Dessert Cafe is a delightful spot combining great coffee with an array of delicious desserts. With its cozy atmosphere and riverside location, it’s a popular hangout for locals. The cafe\'s modern design and friendly service make it an ideal place to enjoy a sweet treat with your coffee.</string>
    <string name="aroiDessert_address">124 Bach Dang, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Vietnam</string>


    <string name="restaurants_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="bars_category">Bars</string>
    <string name="coffee_category">Coffee Shops</string>

    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>


<!--Mobile Treasure Hunt resources-->
    <string name="clue_1_location_name">Man Thai beach, Da Nang</string>
    <string name="clue_1_clue">For people who does\'t know how to swim but still want to float</string>
    <string name="clue_1_hint">Best beach to learn stand-up paddle boarding</string>
    <string name="clue_1_summary">The best beach for sport lover in Da Nang, you will find a lot less tourists here and a lot more local people, they have some street food available/drinks, of course don\'t expect it to be a main beach bar restaurant level, the area is really cool to chill out and have a drink, have a look at the pictures, they have a sup centre next to it if you are coming during the day!</string>
    <string name="clue_1_lat">16.08904196150438</string>
    <string name="clue_1_long">108.24960074304661</string>

    <string name="clue_2_location_name">Ban Co Peak in Son Tra</string>
    <string name="clue_2_clue">Get here if you wan\'t to play chess against a legendary old man</string>
    <string name="clue_2_hint">The stationary Confucius checker</string>
    <string name="clue_2_summary">Hilltop lookout point for views of Da Nang city and the sea, with a pensive, chess-playing statue.</string>
    <string name="clue_2_lat">16.120592581854837</string>
    <string name="clue_2_long">108.27217282527789</string>

    <string name="rules_header">Rules and Requirements</string>

    <string name="rule_1_number">1</string>
    <string name="rule_1_header">Permissions</string>
    <string name="rule_1">GPS permissions are needed to verify you are at the correct location for each clue.</string>

    <string name="rule_2_number">2</string>
    <string name="rule_2_header">Start</string>
    <string name="rule_2">Once you press start below, a timer will begin and you will be taken to your first clue. The faster you find the secret locations, the better!</string>

    <string name="rule_3_number">3</string>
    <string name="rule_3_header">Feeling Stuck?</string>
    <string name="rule_3">Tap the Hint button to reveal another clue on where the location is. Be aware, you only get one hint so think hard!</string>

    <string name="rule_4_number">4</string>
    <string name="rule_4_header">Think you\'ve found it?</string>
    <string name="rule_4">Smack that Found It! button. We\'ll check your location and see if you\'re there.</string>

    <string name="rule_5_number">5</string>
    <string name="rule_5_header">Not At The Right Place?</string>
    <string name="rule_5">Dang! Well, we\'ll keep the timer going so think quick and move on to your next guess.</string>

    <string name="rule_6_number">6</string>
    <string name="rule_6_header">Found The Right Place?</string>
    <string name="rule_6">Found the right place? Boom! If there are any more destinations, you\'ll be directed to the next clue. </string>

    <string name="rule_7_number">7</string>
    <string name="rule_7_header">Found All The Treasure?</string>
    <string name="rule_7">Found all the treasure? Congratulations! You\'ve beat the game. We\'ll let you know how long it took you to finish. Once you\'re ready, you can navigate back to the home page and start again. </string>

    <string name="action_button_text">Start</string>

    <string name="found_it_button">Found It!</string>
    <string name="next_clue_button">Next Clue</string>
    <string name="home_button">Home</string>

    <string name="dialog_title">Are You Sure?</string>
    <string name="dialog_content">Listen… I get it, finding these landmarks can be a tall task. If you quit now, you\’ll lose your progress. This can\’t be undone.</string>
    <string name="quit_button">Quit</string>
    <string name="cancel_dialog_button">Cancel</string>

    <string name="wrong_location_dialog_title">Wrong Location!</string>
    <string name="wrong_location_dialog_content">Not quite there yet. Think back to the clues you have and try again</string>
    <string name="wrong_location_dialog_confirm">Okay</string>

    <string name="timer_header">Total Time Elapsed</string>

    <string name="found_it_header">You found it!</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_complete_header">Congratulations! You\'ve found all the treasure.</string>
</resources>